<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lost Random</title>
    <description>Quixotic dabbler of esoteric arcana...</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:16:32 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 11:16:32 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: SodDL Terrible Beauty</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I took a brief detour from my current Lion &amp;amp; Dragon reading to garner gaming ideas about the Fae kingdoms for a possible Dark Albion campaign. Lucky for me I had the excellent Terrible Beauty (by Robert Schwalb), a Shadow Of The Demon Lord (SotDL) supplement, waiting for me on the bookshelf. Let’s explore the contents shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/post/tb.png&quot; alt=&quot;Terrible Beauty&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pitch from the publisher… 
“ Terrible Beauty presents tools for players and Game Masters to introduce faerie stories, mechanics, and themes into Shadow of the Demon Lord campaigns. Inside, you’ll find:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The elf, hobgoblin, and pixie ancestries.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An assortment of new paths such as the Avowed expert path and the eternal guardian and troll hunter master paths.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Fey tradition, and new spells for existing traditions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Overviews of several sample faerie kingdoms.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New relics such as the Vorpal Sword and a new enchanted object table.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New creatures ranging from the fair nymph to the foul jabberwock.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A complete adventure for expert characters. “&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have run a SotDL mini story arc for my players in the past, and it is a great system that I really enjoy. So, does Terrible Beauty deliver? The answer is a resounding yes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first few sections offer a quick background on the Fae worlds, creating Fae creatures are next, and followed by the expert paths for character advancement. The Faerie background tables and interesting things are worth the price of admission alone, but the master paths filled with potential NPCs materials really get the imagination working. A small list of unique magic spells rounds this section nicely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next is a bit on the lands of the Faerie. Here again you will find a full complementary setting for Dark Albion for an easy to lift to any existing campaign. Pages 28-29 contain a great section of tables, interesting characters, strange sights, and weird events, that will provide tons of random spicy and exotic flavors to your Fae lands. The rest of the section dives into the Fae lands of Alfheim, The Nameless City, Elysium and the Midnight Lands, all truly imaginative locales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Creature of the Faeries section brings a good assortment of varied powered Faerie baddies to life.  One of my favorites is the Bean-Nighe, horrid Fae creatures designed to bring nightmares to life and defoul your players. One of the SotDL strong points, is the concise monster description, stats-block and special attack options that make GMing this game very special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the “My Father Left Forever” expert path adventure, ties all of the elements found in this book. I have not run the adventure yet, but it appears to be spot-on with the horror and weird elements that Shadow of the Demon Lord does really well.  The art, the writing, and the book design are all solid. Terrible Beauty is a highly recommended supplement for any game system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy it here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.drivethrurpg.com/product/179805/Terrible-Beauty&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Terrible Beauty &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/sotdl-terrible-beauty/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/sotdl-terrible-beauty/</guid>
        
        <category>adventure</category>
        
        <category>sotdl</category>
        
        
        <category>rpg</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fresh Start</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the demise of G+ I decided to move my previously anemic private blog from Blogger to GitHub Pages. I hope you enjoy the fresh look and clean interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the Mia Culpa moment where I apologize for not having blogged enough in the past year. I did have an excellent online year in gaming, and I did find a new social media home on &lt;a href=&quot;https://mewe.com/myworld&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MeWe&lt;/a&gt; . I was very happy to see that the Lone Wolf Roleplaying group has also set-up shop there, along with many G+ RPG refugees. See? life is good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog reboot comes the shift in focus from low fantasy to a more heroic, albeit a more futuristic grim-dark world that is Warhammer 40k, which is the dystopian sci-fi version of Warhammer Fantasy; I love them both equally for reasons that I will explain in further future blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it’s with great pleasure that I have signed up for Solo-A-Module-Month (SAMM). A bit of blurb from the organizers …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Last year, the G+ group labeled March as “Solo-A-Module Month”. For the month of March, you are challenged to solo  a published adventure module in whatever way you choose and share your actual plays, strategies, tips &amp;amp; tricks, and  tactics for soloing a module – ideally without spoiling the whole thing for yourself!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am pretty stoked about participating in the SAMM event for March, 2019. The module I have chosen is Fantasy Flight Games Rogue Trader’s the “Forsaken Bounty”.  Rogue Traders are the privateers of the Warhammer 40k world. The siren song of profit and plunder lures these great space captains to the most dangerous unexplored regions of space…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/post/rt.png&quot; alt=&quot;Rogue Trader&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Maw. That is what they call the gateway to the Koronus Expanse; an apt name given its history. As long as I have sat the captain’s throne, I have seen countless ships, and souls, vanish down its gullet. Of course they still come, for the Maw leads to a belly full of riches.” –Lord-Captain Ezekiel Pengalia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the soloist tools of the trade, I will be running the module accompanied by dice and my deck of Sci-Fi GameMaster’s Apprentice cards  that will act as the “Oracle” or game master.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further adieu, fame and fortunes awaits matey’s …&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/a-fresh-start/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/a-fresh-start/</guid>
        
        <category>rpg</category>
        
        <category>wh40k</category>
        
        
        <category>rpg</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
