<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lost Random</title>
    <description>Quixotic dabbler of esoteric arcana...</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 21:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 21:10:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fresh Start</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the demise of G+ I decided to move my previously anemic private blog from Blogger to GitHub Pages. I hope you enjoy the fresh look and clean interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the Mia Culpa moment where I apologize for not having blogged enough in the past year. I did have an excellent online year in gaming, and I did find a new social media home on &lt;a href=&quot;https://mewe.com/myworld&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MeWe&lt;/a&gt; . I was very happy to see that the Lone Wolf Roleplaying group has also set-up shop there, along with many G+ RPG refugees. See? life is good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog reboot comes the shift in focus from low fantasy to a more heroic, albeit a more futuristic grim-dark world that is Warhammer 40k, which is the dystopian sci-fi version of Warhammer Fantasy; I love them both equally for reasons that I will explain in further future blogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it’s with great pleasure that I have signed up for Solo-A-Module-Month (SAMM). A bit of blurb from the organizers …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Last year, the G+ group labeled March as “Solo-A-Module Month”. For the month of March, you are challenged to solo  a published adventure module in whatever way you choose and share your actual plays, strategies, tips &amp;amp; tricks, and  tactics for soloing a module – ideally without spoiling the whole thing for yourself!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am pretty stoked about participating in the SAMM event for March, 2019. The module I have chosen is Fantasy Flight Games Rogue Trader’s the “Forsaken Bounty”.  Rogue Traders are the privateers of the Warhammer 40k world. The siren song of profit and plunder lures these great space captains to the most dangerous unexplored regions of space…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/post/rt.png&quot; alt=&quot;Rogue Trader&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Maw. That is what they call the gateway to the Koronus Expanse; an apt name given its history. As long as I have sat the captain’s throne, I have seen countless ships, and souls, vanish down its gullet. Of course they still come, for the Maw leads to a belly full of riches.” –Lord-Captain Ezekiel Pengalia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the soloist tools of the trade, I will be running the module accompanied by dice and my deck of Sci-Fi GameMaster’s Apprentice cards  that will act as the “Oracle” or game master.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further adieu, fame and fortunes awaits matey’s …&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/a-fresh-start/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/a-fresh-start/</guid>
        
        <category>rpg</category>
        
        
        <category>rpg</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
